megameeting.com 2004-12-05

# Video Conferencing Software, Web Conferences; Live Online Internet Meetings: MegaMeeting.com

_PRIVACY POLICY OF MEGAMEETING.COM_

**YOU MUST BE AT LEAST 14 YEARS OLD TO USE MEGAMEETING.COM AND THE SERVICES. IF YOU ARE NOT AT LEAST 14 YEARS OLD, PLEASE EXIT FROM MEGAMEETING.COM IMMEDIATELY.**

_**100\. Coverage of Privacy Policy.**_

This Privacy Policy concerns nonpublic personal information about you. It applies to information that is personally identifiable to you (such as your name, address, birth date, email address, phone number, and financial information) and that is not otherwise publicly available. It also applies to any list, description, or other grouping of consumers which includes you (and publicly available information pertaining to you) that has been derived using any personally identifiable financial information about you that is not publicly available. 

This Privacy Policy does not cover the conduct of persons not affiliated with Internet MegaMeeting, LLC. This means that this Privacy Policy does not cover parties that Internet MegaMeeting, LLC does not own or control, and that are not under common control with Internet MegaMeeting, LLC. Some non-limiting examples of third parties whose conduct is not covered by the MegaMeeting.com Privacy Policy are Internet Service Providers ("ISPs"), other Members of MegaMeeting.com, other participants in communications you may have using the Services, other users of MegaMeeting.com, visitors to MegaMeeting.com Public Pages, advertisers, and web sites of other persons not under our control to which we provide links. 

Web sites other than MegaMeeting.com which are under the control of Internet MegaMeeting, LLC or its affiliates may have their own separate or additional terms and conditions of use and privacy policy, as displayed or explicitly referenced on such other web sites. 

_**101\. Information Collection and Use.**_

We record and organize information about you from the following sources which may result in records personally identifiable to you: 

Information which your browser reports automatically as part of the network protocol, including your computer's IP address, and the page you requested; 

Information when you visit MegaMeeting.com pages, when you log in, and when you enter promotions and sweepstakes. 

Information which you disclose to us during registration to become a Member, or otherwise to supply us when you use MegaMeeting.com and the Services. This information includes your name, address, birth date, email address, user name, and, where appropriate billing and credit card information used to pay for your transactions with us. We ask your birth date to aid us in excluding children under the age of 14 years from our web site and data bases in order to comply with applicable laws. 

Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others, including the passwords and email addresses of yourself and of the persons who participate in your use of our Services. 

Information about you that is provided to us by third parties with whom we do business. 

_**102\. Disclosure of Nonpublic Personal Information.**_

We do not rent or sell your nonpublic personal information in the ordinary course of our business to any nonaffiliated third party. 

We disclose your nonpublic personal information to nonaffiliated persons as follows: 

(i) when we have your consent to disclose. 

(ii) when we need to share your information in order to provide the product or service you have requested. 

(iii) when we respond to legal process, subpoenas or court orders. 

(iv) when you have violated or threaten to violate the terms of this Agreement and such disclosure is made in connection with our exercise of our rights. 

We also reserve rights to disclose your nonpublic personal information to nonaffiliated third parties as follows: 

(v) the right to make a confidential disclosure in connection with sale, merger, refinancing, recapitalization, or other reorganization of our entire business, or of substantial divisions of our business, provided that the disclosures are made in confidence only for the purposes of such a contemplated transaction and for carrying on the same or a related business following such transaction, and provided that the person in receipt of the disclosure is required to maintain privacy policies at least as restrictive as our applicable privacy policies; 

(vi) as otherwise permitted by law, including without limitation the exceptions in 16 CFR 313.13, 313.14, and 313.15. 

__**_103\. Your Right to Opt Out of Disclosures of Nonpublic Personal Information._**

At the time you register to become a Member of MegaMeeting.com you are provided a check-off box on the registration page which gives you an opportunity to opt out of disclosures of your nonpublic personal information to a nonaffiliated third party. If you are registered as a Member of MegaMeeting.com, you also may log onto MegaMeeting.com, then click on the link ‘YourAccount.MegaMeeting.com' to enter or edit your choices concerning future disclosure of your nonpublic personal information to third parties not affiliated with Internet MegaMeeting, LLC. You also may call the following toll-free telephone number to opt out of disclosures of your nonpublic personal information to unaffiliated third parties: 

_**104\. Communications From Which You Cannot Opt Out.**_

Internet MegaMeeting.com reserves the right to send you certain communications without giving you a right to opt out from receipt of them. The communications for which no opportunity to opt out is provided include service announcements, administrative messages, notices and demands required or permitted by law, amendments to the Agreement and the Privacy Policy, and communications concerning the rights of you, us, or any other persons affected by MegaMeeting.com or the Services. 

You are not provided any opportunity to opt out of protocols which are part of the function of MegaMeeting.com and the Services and that are likely to disclose some personal information about you to third parties not affiliated with Internet MegaMeeting, LLC. For example, your browser must provide an IP address to exchange communications. As another example, it is an essential part of the functional protocol for Hosted meetings using the Services of MegaMeeting.com that the Member acting as Host is supplied with a valid user name and a valid, functional email address (and sometimes additional personal identification information) for each person who requests participation in a Host's session so that the Host can exercise a right of consent to each participant. Internet MegaMeeting, LLC does not obtain control over persons merely by accepting registration of them as Members of MegaMeeting.com or by their participation in use of the Services during Host's session. A Member acting as a Host therefore is an unaffiliated third party that receives and could collect such information concerning prospective participants in a manner which is beyond the practical control of Internet MegaMeeting, LLC. Similarly, a Host must provide prospective participants with means to identify a particular Host for a particular session in connection with requests for participation in that Host's particular session, and such prospective participants are third parties unaffiliated with Internet MegaMeeting, LLC who could record that information. 

_**105\. Editing Your MegaMeeting.com Account Information.**_

If you have registered as a Member of MegaMeeting.com you may log on using your User ID and password, then click on the link YourAccount.MegaMeeting.com to edit your registration information, to change your preferences, and to unsubscribe from portions or all categories of future marketing communications from Internet MegaMeeting, LLC and its affiliates. Some of your registration information cannot be completely deleted because that information may be required to send you necessary communications and notices even after your account is terminated. To enable us to limit risks of fraud and abuse of our services and systems, it may take up to 90 days to fully implement some editing changes which you request to your account and this is particularly true of requests to terminate and delete a Member's account. Even after 90 days it is possible that certain information may be retained in off-line backup systems, though we will endeavor to remove terminated accounts from our on-line data bases within 90 days. 

_**106\. Security and Confidentiality.**_

We have physical, electronic and procedural protections to safeguard personal information about you. We limit access to personal information about you to those of our employees and to our service providers who, in our opinion, reasonably need access to such information to provide you with products and services your have requested, or for them to do their work. 

_**107\. Cookies.**_

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes a unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and is stored on your computer's hard drive. 

Each web site can send its cookie to your browser if your browser allows cookies. Generally, your browser only permits a particular web site to access the cookies that particular web site has previously sent to your browser and does not permit other browsers to access cookies sent to you by web sites other than that particular one. 

Most browsers allow you to set preferences to accept all cookies, to reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is set. You must check your browser's "help" menu to determine your browser's capabilities and to select the preferences which your browser offers you. 

_**108\. Our Use of Cookies.**_

Many MegaMeeting.com Pages and Services do not require a cookie. However, certain products or services may require that you log in and permit use of a cookie. If your browser is set to reject all cookies, or if your browser is set to notify you and request your consent to set a cookie and you fail to give your consent, then MegaMeeting.com will be unable to provide you that product or service. 

Internet MegaMeeting, LLC may use its own cookies for a variety of purposes including but not limited to: 

To recall your information when you log in so that we can provide you with customized services. 

To monitor the amount of time which elapses without activity by you while you remain logged onto one of the Services; this is to enable automatic termination of your log-on for the purpose of protecting you against others using your unattended, logged-on account if you do not respond to a request to re-enter your password after a period of inactivity. 

To keep track of the preferences you state when you use MegaMeeting.com or the Services. 

To monitor use of MegaMeeting.com and the Services for the purposes of improving our products and services. 

To determine the size and characteristics of our user base and traffic. 

To offer you appropriate products and services based upon your prior use and preferences. 

_**109\. Other Persons' Use of Cookies.**_

MegaMeeting.com does not monitor or control the content which Members, participants, or other users transmit or exchange using MegaMeeting.com or the Services. It is possible that the content sent to you during a session using the Services, or that you download from postings by other users to a MegaMeeting.com Public Page, could contain a cookie sent to your browser by another participant in that Session or Public Page. The cookies of such nonaffiliated third parties are subject to their own privacy policies, if any, and are not under the control of Internet MegaMeeting, LLC . It is your responsibility to configure your browser and any related software to monitor and control the use of cookies by other users during your use of MegaMeeting.com and the Services. 

_**110\. Contacting Us.**_

You may contact us about confidentiality or security issues at _**admin@MegaMeeting.com**_. 

You may contact us about privacy issues at _**admin@MegaMeeting.com**_. 

You may give us feed back as _**admin@MegaMeeting.com**_. 

You may access your account as Member to edit it if you log on and then click on this link: _**youraccount.megameeting.com**_. 

_**111\. Printer Friendly Versions.**_

For a printer friendly version of the MegaMeeting.com Privacy Policy _CLICK HERE_

For a printer friendly version of the MegaMeeting.com User Agreement _CLICK HERE_
